I'm
one. One.
Where
the
are. The or for.
The OR or
the
or the or or.
The
person
the
person.
Where. The OR.
The OR which.
One
. Or the girl
read the
role right
all
right
Berle for World her for.
Her little.
Girl right.
Ross Berle rag
Brad Renfro
the Paris
for Red Bull
Run
the poor the World
War World War or the boyfriend
the birds and. The
already have to like the section want to
turn south which I wrote mountains are ace
but I was the last time we had it that
way leads them up I don't want to
separately but I don't set for labor.
The idea. I guess I. Might just pick up
a drink in Mexicali. Remember for
about what they have but the.
She's probably dead by now that was
a long time. Bomb as no
one is going to tell the
story. You know except for the
war this is the first time I've been away
from audience kids going to turn back the
come this far. Back to Cal is
a good. Maybe
. That's why.
You're.
Trying to.
Get many of those good idea to be maybe the
making of which I just didn't even the
series is the place and your own
writing on it that's just being
a famous one that would just
think that as not a lot
a gal. Yelp. Sign friend knows it.
Can't sleep mad it would.
I guess yeah I've been.
Nice actually pick up some gas
and drive back. But not that I.
Feel like you. Most.
Know. They don't.
Thanks front. And keep driving.
Sure I'm at Meyers. Do what I tell
you and then I go fast moves are
a lot of dead heroes
back there get nervous.
From now on while you're driving keep
both hands on it will you keep one hand
a lot of top of the seat. The
other hand I not window.
Turn up the next side road we come to.
Open the glove compartment.
But the box cottage is
twenty two given to me.
Was it. This is how we get out
after this first communicate. And we
all get out the same side this one I get
out first then you stand away from the car
and then you. Go.
Rapid jackets around your elbows.
Turn around. We're going
to open the trunk most.
Pull your jacket set. You
up on the truss rod to keep
your hands on THE LEAD. Some of the caged.
I get the blankets. Never
make it. Get the groceries.
Those got it but I like to shoot yeah so I
buy more than you don't
try the smart with.
The US.
I told you my name was yours once
Gilbert bone. Is Right Collins.
But you do for a living.
And the traps. He runs
a garage. Makes you smarter. But that's.
The stuff you want to be all over that which
got lucky it had an empty chamber but
had to use it
a while back I don't make any more fast
moves that I talk to the last guy made that
mistake.
The law I.
Want to do back. The particular
time. Yeah we told our lives to
expect this home and we got
their wives. And kids I
which just keep thinking how nice
it will be to see them again.
At the checkpoints but I know
talking by giving the word step on.
The world the same.
Silo.
A car is very good. I go where I'm
going to go so I'd. Probably gone.
Oh nice pump fill up with gas we
got a road map. I got an idea. For
a good. Few
discussing it that's
a big thing was you I told you he doesn't
understand English and I don't understand
Mexico never mind the
change let's get out of.
There me the map.
Take the first side road we come to.
Key All right now get out like I told you.
If you're the smart guy spread
the map out on the hood.
It's
a hand up on the car but for
dogs that are obsolete it. Out
far. That's five hundred
a month is it on the Gulf of
California. Say anything about
a ferry across the Gulf. Friday. And then.
We loaded with. We can make that easy.
After that I won't be needing
you guys anymore. And I
guess we won't be having
rabbit then. I wasn't trying.
COLLINS But I can on that rock that.
Given the map.
That that one the other one. That.
I counted but they can't back on the rock.
Again this is about it too I say
you try yeah good you ought.
To have.
Bougherra. You know we're going to hurt
your buddies good with guys. Crazy I want
to what just again good.
God is our club the very.
Heart of our youth. Vote across the.
Government trying to get my message that
time. Heals.
All right. The vast.
Vast vast. Vast.
Vast. Vast.
Amount go get going.
Nervous relax. When I
come on come on I had.
Fun going over what. You
guys were good players what.
We're for the with the
surface.
Silence. Columns. How do
you want to turn on the
radio why bother I guess
Mexican commercials about my.
I think. It's something
else. Like one of those
those guys from the.
Schedule for ten o'clock to. The crime
front the police of Western states from
Washington to Colorado and Utah. To keep
a continuous search for
the Kansas. Fire reports
a place the killer in Florida.
Over the last twenty four hours.
Latest victim. Of an Oregon. Yesterday in
a county California victim's car possibly
with fire is going to it's not yet been
found United Nations
resolution near unanimous.
And that even close. You
guys don't have to worry.
You're going to start sweating
when they put me in this car.
And they're good evening ladies and gentlemen
this is Sam is reporting the news at
the top of the news tonight is the real
thought of the hitchhike motor and admires
those deadlines Yesterday the devil from
that other ride and William Johnson apart
then asked him to hop in now William Johnson
has been going all out ever Clavering
admires the play that set up roadblocks at
all the dry weight of the western states
that all water station I.V.
Closely watched by just like twenty eight
year debate is putting a doctor doctor
a father and
a black leather jacket but I'm going to
find the paralyzed and the ones that have
any information regarding aware about to
begin to make communicate with you here at
the place of the Federal
Bureau of Investigation world.
Case. Out.
If you take one.
Get around the cost. Of capital.
And what you think you balance. Every get
a chance. You guys are
going to die that's.
Just
a question of when. Santa Rosa Lee
is. At the end of the line. If
the cops find
a way to gather. All right he checks. And
you wait for the attack it's all right
this. Any way you can tell I was awake or
asleep. At slumber I'm
a. Post
a quote. A good. We're
getting out here and buy some grub we got
the car like usual you guys going to
store ahead of me now Mexican I'm talking
to you I tell you how much you pay that
player. Now one other thing I'm going to
have my hand in my pocket shelf I reckon
I'm actually clean I want to
keep it that way let's go.
When this is.
It's. A.
Little getting out of this you want to thank
you that's what people that prove that
you live over as I was that I was pretty
good he didn't take one but he said I feel
I said that prices are about the
same as. Never mind the kid.
But he wants some beans and stuff and
tomato soup I like that get four cans he
wants for
a can of beans for cans of tomato soup
three cans of chili. Now yes he doesn't
understand English well you're not talking
Max but the cans of the shelves get in
the columns.
I can take some more.
I don't call this. Kings and vessels as
a DI was that it was. The
Santa Barbara in the summer. That are away
from the and I. Was
a kid out let's get out your car god I
thought it was English which are not just.
Like those that cause you. But your so
are you with that but I just say to her.
I said Go you with God which was.
A mistake to do in that central idea
there's I'm going that nice place her.
Old. Home alone.
Won't. Hold.
A lot.
And.
I've been.
Working at the watch
bought. My wife gave it
a. Drought over. This
year hammy I told you
to throw it over here.
But.
I don't wash I guess once when I
was seventeen. Nobody gave it
I took the proper welcome that choice
to one of the objects outside itself.
Was essential. You guys sell off.
You know what makes you happy.
If the next in aisle you
is stuck. You scared to get
out of your own I always had
a good series of. Let me.
Nobody ever gave me an
icee so I don't know.
Why folks would. When I was born it took
one look at this push to mine and tell me
to get lost I didn't need
a need that you got what I wanted my oh
you got to know how in
a few bucks to plug. You can buy
anything anybody especially
if you've got them at the point of
a gun that really scares you
have been at the other end of
a gun you know and never will
I'm going to listen to them.
Tear it up like I was going you just get
the grub ready anything interesting I'll
let you know. I gotta find an
excuse to raise the hood of
a complicated radio out of commission. For
Sammy finds out they're looking for us
together with throw him on the radio I'm
Not Gonna Take It Anymore we gotta get him
you can't beat him that way. You give him
one good reason to kill us we gotta take
the chance as long as he meets us we'll
stay alive when he gets ready to jump us
will jump him up before
maybe today maybe tomorrow.
All right. If found Johnson's car.
You know I'm in Mexico and they're
looking for you too in the chocolate mom
where the chocolate mom. And I are is on
a whole not Mexico now what do you know
so you tell your wives you're
going and you can the Mexican
one for. The bunch of initiating
you still causing all
the trouble tellin lies
I got everybody and his brother
looking for in the mountains.
I told to turn the radio I
did. Takes time to warm up
why try another station when there's.
The old.
The rule the thank. The
gods are good. But I'm going to put back.
The the.
Back further.
Shall watch. One.
One.
When he hit
but.
The tools in the back. Looked. Good.
So you.
Give an accurate description
of my. State. Of the
store.
It seems to be heading south all right
staying clear of all main highways exactly
now to the west this is lawless barren and
would afford no means of escape his most
logical move would be.
None of those ideas. Then.
One must. Do that by the. Book Club.
I'm going down.
I hope I'm going to cause I have faith.
That they are alive last good God.
That I'm alive what are you trying
to do record God like I tell you.
Out. What I said John I've
done that spare time
I'll go to work though.
You keep working keep your trap shut
no matter what I'll be watching.
Right now that you're. Telling me
that all we have manufactured.
A place on.
The search for Gilbert Bowen and Roy Collins
now believed to have been last seen
with Emmett Meyers mass killer being stepped
up by the our helicopter to work our
fire area but now that's about California
the planes are maintaining close liaison
with the ground reporting isolated card
camera the mixed feelings about Joyce and
bring great I get.
That I don't know we're not going to get
me no says unknown but some of them got
out there Monica I'm not going to let up I
don't get on badly or get the good they
don't end up on just a little going to
sell another glance of the homeless fellow
a cop would look
a little. You
know what I know to look
at this on another go as
a normal up with whatever you foresee
that meant this but I don't say this but
first it got me to shooting
at one of those up
a set or so but he is the. One that I meet
and I thought I must come up with the
skill that was a key
to this which was just
a comedy skit on with us so that I mean
look I mean what I said what I mean and
which of us has been either.
The button there is that it's
a quick read of whatever sort of grabs.
It has.
The you.
Know the world with.
All that right there. Oh. Around.
The. World. Break the lock.
Yes. After the. Oh
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh. Oh oh
oh. OK I want to be on the.
Rock. Right. Rocked just
stopped just asked asd stabbed
just rubbed out Oh but it just brushed
past but. It just.
Bored me Beryl. The whole time you.
And Congress to New York by guess what
you know if you're not going to. Be.
Born. You'll see
the front of. Now as you will notice
when interrogated that the roadblock the
man and his wife were very definite in
their statement that they only saw two men
this was. They the point however which we
feel is of importance the couple stated
that the behavior of the men seemed strange
that their actions to talk to the.
Possibility that till now by covering
the two men were to account for their
behavior following through on that possibility
now on the assumption that Maurice
is listening to the car radio we're
issuing these broadcasts in the states
containing false information as to his
whereabouts and connecting with the man with
him we appreciate your cooperation
and following the same procedure.
It's not to be the main highway you know
as I mean it's like an abandoned Astra.
And it's OK for tonight
and over there. You.
Already run the rock still trying
to talk me out of it and I have got
a chance to get my I credit your one on
if for no lottery General good to get I
told you I get
a break I'm going to take it you'll
do whatever you want I. Crosser
of its.
Early. Days
Gone.
You guys are really like you take
a look. But I was asleep.
You know you begin to
get out is. I don't like. The cut.
But it's all washed up.
Or are for the informed
bulletin for the.
Old. Place.
Over there. Oh.
The Blues.
You prolly tarragon that chair.
Ice and the.
This is fine got out of you're going to
kill us do it get it although I'm not going
to kill it without
a reason go get the rest and
goods out of the car and have
a real good meal.
Favor of the next get it
fixed if. Anything you say.
You're up with are if you think that you
apply for the California at Mexican police
officials have abandoned their
because they have they already have
a pirated connected with the
disappearance of Gilbert bought
a bike out on the bell
central California they have
a missing that last Sunday
by about the bay on
a patron plate on both sides of the border
now below the pirate is traveling alone
as
a parody of back to the second making escape
by way of Fattah called the LIA. Well
you know. It's going to change my plans.
It's like you and me are going fishing
after all. I have feet and so that
guy let's go. When I'm gone anyplace. That
ab.
What you're doing is
a great big hole in that crank. All
right we'll walk this way that
so our angle of us needs Collins
a nice long hike.
Gap. I got
a fishing gear out of the back oh.
oh Oh. Oh
.
I'll.
Stay with
a little bit yes you're
alive. That's again. Get
down to
a low voltage.
Let's get going.
Maybe we'll have to leave
you here. Too bad.
Come on really try.
Why
her
where
. Or. The wayside. With
the challenge caught up with
the American. Out of my job.
The it was. The IT job that.
The and
the Mole all that just sees the bright and
the
and.
The
The and.
The bright lights.
Relaxed.
But I had as you can
stand I felt the stuff.
In Oakland and just about my size which in
a black shirt and dives
and. A leather jacket. And
let's respect and with my. That
is what I was. And nobody and
satirize alay ever saw it. But change.
Clothes. At
a bag and take your clothes off and one.
Of the best. The last.
Time I Get up when. All
at the old.
The
old the back got the gold I.
Hold.
The
old.
Book by. The
side
of
a. Third straight you won't
be there long caught.
The cops down there they might. Be
a problem for the. Not
if they found they made
a mistake they wouldn't. Let someone will
join adds. I might even buy you boys
a big movie.
That isn't your. Three big.
Mistake and. I want you
to talk myself tell you.
So if. You can talk.
About the fright of blindness I'll be
watching his face if he starts looking for.
Friday that today. Where we catch.
The second five hundred. Thirty
burned up being repaired
alive line. If you know
anyone speaks English.
As
a customer speaks English. Their
talk you can be pretty
much going to see it done.
What can I do for you. I want to find out
about the furtive glance of one of the
fishing SO BAD VERY more for the
next two months maybe she burned
out. Fishing is pretty good here
that is why much or not but again
you have motor boat you know someone is
a boat sure sure my friend I mean he
had one model run schools how do we
get to this Jaime in the mine where he
works. Not finish until six I think that for
you tomorrow morning I want to go now. At
six by the time my friend gets the boat
ready there is no sun. My friend does
not like using too much for his night.
Caesar's wife and kids good
morning or night for me.
You pay my friend Bill. You'll be
a beer and heat during the
name of the body of. A
thousand thanks in your.
Go around the weight of
the water till it starts.
Whole of them in
a way to. Hang on. Better
go fishing when you get
a chance I said you came down here
for was in this. You guys are really
full. If you weren't one of
you want to get away. But you
kept thinking about each other
same as some chance. You got tired
slow down. Now it's pretty
late. Tomorrow I'll
be in Glamis. To badge and I'm
making the whole trip with.
That be kind of silly when.
You'll stay quiet. You smile
just like your clothes kill your
make attack oneness but they'll catch up
with you and put you out of your misery.
You haven't got a chance you haven't got
a chain except that God. Because
without it she had not yet
finished.
God number. From the family that
one of the our if you want to set
a country not only be able to buy but not
a life they are made by God The manual I
mean. No God or of only what I told him of
the body here. But all but
all the body the son I
know somebody because. One room.
When.
One.
When. All.
Are come and now you get to take
a nice little walk all by yourself down
the alley and out of the dock me and bone
will fall if you try to tip anyone off
a leg ball Abbott you wouldn't want
that to happen what you get got.
One.
Room.
One. One.
What.
what What
.
Go ahead come on. All the way
out to get out of the like.
One
.
I don't call.
The
earth
the
earth but this great book. There was
a those employers year old. Guy
. During. Practice.
That. The third. Gen.
I'm sorry we have to have we're
bored you understand. That.
It's all right.
The wrath of
a. Whole
World.